RG 005:029, Office of the Governor: Raymond E. Baldwin (1943-1946)
Connecticut State Library
- Series 2. Subject Files, 1946-10
  - Personnel Dept., 1946 (Box 469)
  - Petroleum Administration for War (Box 469)
  - Pharmacy, Board of (Box 469)
  - Pipe Line - Fuel (Box 469)
  - Plant Strikes, 2 folders (Box 470)
  - Plymouth Probate Court, 1943 (Box 470)
  - Police - 44 Letters from People Referred to State Police Dept., 1945 (Box 470)
  - Police - Letters from People Referred to State Police Dept., 1946 (Box 470)
  - Police - Letters from People Referred to State Police Dept. (Box 470)
  - Police - Commissioner Hickey & Officers (Box 470)
  - Police Reports (Box 470)
  - Port Authority Study Commission (Box 470)
  - Post-War Building Fund (Box 470)
  - Post-War Foreign Trade (Box 470)
  - Post-War Planning - Agriculture (Box 470)
  - Post-War Planning - Banking (Box 470)
  - Post-War Planning - Education Committee (Box 470)
  - Post-War Planning - Foreign Export Trade Meeting, 1943 November 8 (Box 470)
  - Post-War Planning - Fund (Box 470)
  - Post-War Planning - Letters to be Referred to Board (Box 470)
  - Post-War Planning - Public Works Program (Box 470)
  - Post-War Planning Board - Correspondence with Members of Board (Box 470)
  - Post-War Planning Board - General, 3 folders (Box 471)
  - Post -War Planning Board - Industry and Labor Committee (Box 471)
  - Post-War Planning Board - Membership (Box 471)
  - Post-War Planning Board - Minutes of Meeting (Box 471)
  - Post-War Planning Board - Small Businesses (Box 471)
  - Post-War Planning Committee - Medical Care and Health (Box 471)
  - Post-War Time Magazine (Box 471)
  - Press Release Re: Danbury, Governor Raymond E. Baldwin, 1946 October 29 (Box 471)
  - Press Release by Governor Raymond E. Baldwin, Hartford, Conn. Mfg. Assoc., Bushnell Memorial, 1946 October 30 (Box 471)
  - Press Release Stratford, Connecticut October 22, 1946, 1946 October 22 (Box 471)
  - Press Release Wallingford By Governor Raymond E. Baldwin, October 30, 1946, 1946 October 30 (Box 471)
  - O[ffice] of P[rice] A[dministration] Price Control Meeting, 1946 July 5 (Box 471)
  - O[ffice] of P[rice] A[dministration] Price Control Meeting, 1946 July 9 (Box 471)
  - Prison, State (Box 471)
  - Probate Courts (Box 472)
  - Psycho - Neurotic Cases (Box 472)
  - Public Utilities Commission (Box 472)
  - Public Utilities - Western Union - Postal Telegraph Cons[olidation] (Box 472)
  - Public Welfare Council (2 folders) (Box 472)
  - Public Works Department (Box 472)
  - Public Works Programs (Box 472)
  - Purchasing Division (Box 472)
  - Radio Broadcasts - Governor Baldwin - "You Are a Government" Program, Station WDRC, 1946 April 2 (Box 472)
  - Recorded Broadcast by Governor Baldwin Re: Visit to Ft. Devens, Mass., 1945 December 3 (Box 472)
  - Recording by Governor Baldwin WICC Anniversary, 1946 August 1 (Box 472)
  - Recording by Governor Baldwin, Station WONS - Hartford "Vacation Message - People of New England", 1946 July 19 (Box 472)
  - Recording by Governor Baldwin - Middletown State Hospital, Broadcast over WTHT, WELI, WATR, 1945 November 13 (Box 472)
  - Recreation Committee (Box 472)
  - Rehabilitation of Veterans (Box 472)
  - Rehabilitation Program (Box 472)
  - Remarks by Governor Raymond E. Baldwin - Conn. League of Women Voters - Station WTIC, 1944 October 14 (Box 472)
  - Remarks by Governor Raymond E. Baldwin - Inter-American Institute, St. Joseph's College - West Hartford, 1945 April 3 (Box 472)
  - Remarks by Governor Raymond E. Baldwin - Norwalk Town Hall Association - 10-11-44 (Box 472)
  - Remarks by Governor Raymond E. Baldwin - Opening Ceremonies of the Red Cross War Fund Drive, 1945 March 1 (Box 472)
  - Remarks by Governor Raymond E. Baldwin - Plumbers and Steamfitters Convention - New Britain, 1944 October 14 (Box 472)
  - Remarks by Governor Raymond E. Baldwin - Red Cross Luncheon - Hotel Bond - March 11, 1946 (Box 472)
  - Remarks by Governor Raymond E. Baldwin to the Republican Town Chairmen, et al., Hotel Bond, 1944 November 1 (Box 472)
  - Remarks by Governor Raymond E. Baldwin - Selective Service Award Ceremony - Hall of House, 1946 March 27 (Box 472)
  - Rent Control (Box 472)
  - Resettlement (Box 472)
  - Retirement Commission (Box 472)
  - Rex Brasher Commission (Box 472)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson, Dinner in Honor of - Hartford Club - Invitations and Acceptances, 1945 April 10 (Box 472)
  - Royal Typewriter Company (Box 472)
  - Saint Francis Hospital (Box 472)
  - Salvage Drive Scrap Metal (Box 472)
  - Salvage Program (Box 472)
  - Savings Banks (Box 472)
  - Savings Banks Life Insurance Fund Trus[t] (Box 472)
  - Savings Banks' Railroad Investment Committee (Box 472)
  - School Lunches (Box 472)
  - Scrap Drive (Box 472)
  - Sculpture Commission (Box 472)
  - Secretary of Labor, United States (Box 472)
  - Secretary of State, Washington (Box 472)
  - Secretary of the State [Connecticut] (Box 472)
  - Selective Service - Classification Advice from State Headquarters (Box 473)
  - Selective Service - Deferments (Box 473)
  - Selective Service - Deferments, State Committee on (Box 473)
  - Selective Service - Farming Rules and Regulations (Box 473)
  - Selective Service - General Corres[pondence] (Box 473)
  - Selective Service - Manpower Division (Box 473)
  - Selective Service - Reemployment Committee Men for Local Draft Boards (Box 473)
  - Selective Service - Rehabilitation of the Veteran Within Industry (Box 473)
  - Shell Fish Commission (Box 473)
  - Sheriffs, Correspondence with (Box 473)
  - Smaller War Plants Indexes (Box 473)
  - Social Security (Box 473)
  - Society for Crippled Children (Box 473)
  - Soil Conservation Committee (Box 473)
  - Soldiers' Home, Rocky Hill (Box 473)
  - Soldiers', Sailors' and Marines' Fund (Box 473)
  - Solid Fuel Emergency - 1946 (Box 473)
  - Solid Fuels Pricing Policy (Box 473)
  - Speeches (Box 473)
    - Acceptance Speech (Nomination for Governor), 1944 August 8 (Box 473)
    - Agenda for Special Session of General Assembly, WTIC, 1944 January 4 (Box 473)
    - Agriculture - Room New Haven - Station WICC, 1943 April 20 (Box 473)
    - Air Raids - Dimout - McKenzie Veto, 1943 May 4 (Box 473)
    - American Legion Convention - Eastern Point, Groton, 1943 June 18 (Box 473)
    - Automobile Club, March 10, 1943, 1943 March 10 (Box 473)
    - Ban on Pleasure Driving, 1943 June 1 (Box 473)
    - Budget - Proceedings of General Assembly, 1943 March 30 (Box 473)
    - Budget - General Assembly, 1943 April 27 (Box 473)
    - The Circus Fire - War Council Broadcast, 1944 July 15 (Box 473)
    - The Civilian War Jobs - War Council Broadcast, 1944 June 7 (Box 473)
    - Commencement Exercise - Wilbraham Academy, Wilbraham, Mass, 1944 January 23 (Box 473)
    - Conn. Agriculture - Initial speech by Governor R. E. Baldwin in Tuesday Evening Series, 1943 January 12 (Box 473)
    - Conn. Cancer Society Dinner Meeting - WTIC - 8:30-9:00 o'clock, 1946 January 8 (Box 473)
    - Conn. Farm Forum - 4-H Club Mobilization, 1944 March 4 (Box 473)
    - Conn. Federation of Labor - Hotel Elton - Waterbury, 1945 January 10 (Box 473)
    - Conn. On the Alert - War Council, 1943 April 4 (Box 473)
    - Conn. Victory Manpower Campaign - War Council Broadcast - February 21, 1944, 1944 February 21 (Box 473)
    - "Connecticut's Role in the War Effort During 1944" - War Council Broadcast - WTIC, 1943 December 28 (Box 473)
    - Convention of Conn. Federation of Labor, 1944 September 9 (Box 473)
    - Danbury City Election - Transcribed Station WTHT - WICC, 1945 March 26 (Box 473)
    - Dedication of Atwater Memorial Library, North Branford, 1943 (Box 473)
    - Dedication of Service Flag, Knights of Columbus, New Haven, 1944 April 16 (Box 473)
    - Development Commission - 5th Anniversary - Neill's Farm, 1944 August 17 (Box 473)
    - Dinner in Honor of Governor and Mrs. Bricker, Norwalk, 1944 September 23 (Box 473)
    - "Dunbar and Oaks Rally", Bushnell Memorial, 3 p.m., 1945 April 29 (Box 473)
    - Employment and Labor - Station WICC - Bridgeport, 1944 October 13 (Box 473)
    - Excerpts from by Governor Baldwin at Fairfield County Women's Republican Association, Stamford, 1944 September 26 (Box 473)
    - Fairfield College Preparatory School, June 16, 1943, 1943 June 16 (Box 473)
    - Farm Bureau Federation - Bond Hotel, Re: Child Care, Etc., 4-H Clubs, 1944 January 7 (Box 473)
    - Farm Forum - War Council, 1944 June 17 (Box 473)
    - Farm and Home Day - University of Connecticut, 1944 August 2 (Box 473)
    - Flag Day - Independence Hall - Philadelphia, PA, 1944 June 14 (Box 473)
    - Food Production - War Gardens - 48 Hour Week - Groton-New London Bridge, 1943 March 2 (Box 473)
    - Fortune Broadcast - 7:00 p.m. - Forum, 1944 March 30 (Box 473)
    - Forced War Loan Drive - WTIC, 1944 January 18 (Box 473)
    - Fuel, 1943 January 18 (Box 473)
    - Fuel, 1943 February 23 (Box 473)
    - Fuel - Women in Industry, 1943 January 26 (Box 473)
    - General Electric Company at Schenectady - and other Correspondence on subject, 1943 October 29 (Box 474)
    - Governor 's Conference at Columbus, Ohio, 1943 June 21 (Box 474)
    - Groton, New London Bridge Dedication, 1943 February 20 (Box 474)
    - Hall of Flags, 1945 February 16 (Box 474)
    - Hamilton Standard Propeller Corporation - War Bond Rally, 1944 February 1 (Box 474)
    - Hartford Advertising Club, 1944 October 17 (Box 474)
    - Hartford County Women's Republican Club, 1943 November 12 (Box 474)
    - Highway Fund, 1943 April 13 (Box 474)
    - Home Food Production and Preservation Conference, 1944 February 24 (Box 474)
    - Horace Wells Centenary Celebration - Hartford Club, 1944 December 11 (Box 474)
    - Housatonic Valley Regional High School, 1943 June 18 (Box 474)
    - Independence Day Celebration - Hall of Flags, State Capitol, Hartford, 1944 July 4 (Box 474)
    - Industrial Training Conference, Woolsey Hall, New Haven, 1943 December 4 (Box 474)
    - Inter-American Conference - Reception, Bond Hotel, Hartford, 1944 May 23 (Box 474)
    - Inter-American Luncheon - Bond Hotel, Hartford, 1944 September 28 (Box 474)
    - Introducing Nelson E. Rockefeller - West Middle School, 1945 April 10 (Box 474)
    - Introduction of Paul V. McNutt - Meriden, 1944 March 20 (Box 474)
    - Kiwanis Club, New York, 1944 January 5 (Box 474)
    - Labor Day - Mackinac Island, Michigan, 1943 September 5 (Box 474)
    - Launching of Submarine Caiman, Electric Boat Company, 1944 March 30 (Box 474)
    - Madame Chiang-Kai-Shek's Reception, New York, 1943 March 2 (Box 474)
    - Material for 1944 Campaign (Box 474)
    - Meeting of Mayors and Selectmen Re: Plans for Reemployment, 1944 January 21 (Box 474)
    - "Meet the Men of the Victory Fleet" - Radio Broadcast USUN, Florida, 1944 July 26 (Box 474)
    - Meeting of the Mary Silliman Chapter, DAR, Bridgeport, 1943 May 10 (Box 474)
    - Middlesex Club, Boston, Mass., 1944 February 12 (Box 474)
    - Middletown High School Commencement, 1944 June 15 (Box 474)
    - Middletown Honor Roll, 1943 November 11 (Box 474)
    - Speech on Mile of Dimes, 1943 January 15 (Box 474)
    - Speech on Mile of Dimes, 1944 January 14 (Box 474)
    - Milk Supply - WTIC, WELI, WNLC, WICC, 1943 October 16 (Box 474)
    - Mutual Savings Bank, New York City, 1944 May 11 (Box 474)
    - National Inter-Fraternity Conference, New York City, 1943 November 26 (Box 474)
    - New Britain State Teachers' College, 1943 October 23 (Box 474)
    - New England Governor's Conference at Boston, 1943 November 18-19 (Box 474)
    - New Haven Chamber of Commerce, 1944 April 21 (Box 474)
    - New Haven Clock Company, 1944 October 31 (Box 474)
    - New Haven County Republican Women's Association, Hotel Guarde, New Haven, 1944 September 25 (Box 474)
    - New Jersey Chamber of Commerce, 1944 February 15 (Box 474)
    - New York Credit Men's Association, The Waldorf Astoria, 1944 February 8 (Box 474)
    - Nurse Improvements, 1943 March 4 (Box 474)
    - Opening of the Greater Hartford Veterans Service Center, 1944 September 24 (Box 474)
    - Opening of New Haven Latin American Products Exhibit, Hotel Taft, New Haven, 1945 February 5 (Box 474)
    - Pending Legislation - War Powers Bill - War Council, Defense Council, 1943 January 19 (Box 474)
    - Proceedings of Governors' Conference at Columbus Ohio, 1943 June 22 (Box 474)
    - Real Estate Board of New York, 1943 February 6 (Box 474)
    - Reconversion - Station WDRC -, 1944 September 15 (Box 474)
    - Reconversion Program, 1944 September 13 (Box 474)
    - Recreation Conference - War Council - Waterbury, 1944 April 21 (Box 474)
    - Red Cross Drive, 1943 March 1 (Box 474)
    - Red Cross War Fund Opening Ceremonies, 1944 March 1 (Box 474)
    - Reemployment of Servicemen - War Council Broadcast - January 25, 1944, 1944 January 25 (Box 474)
    - Reference to Chiang-Kai-Shek - War Powers Bill - Arms Production - Hours of Women in Industry, 1943 March 9 (Box 474)
    - Republican Women's Association of Rhode Island, 1943 November 5 (Box 474)
    - Republican State Convention held at Bangor, Maine, 1944 April 14 (Box 474)
    - Republican Women of the State at Hotel Bond, 1943 March 15 (Box 474)
    - Special Session of Legislature, 1944 January 24 (Box 474)
    - Special Session of Legislature, 1944 June 19-20 (Box 474)
    - Stafford Fair, 1943 October 2 (Box 474)
    - State Finances, Bond Retirement and Post-War Purposes, 1943 April 6 (Box 474)
    - Summing Up of Legislative Doings - Typical Conn. Family, 1943 May 18 (Box 474)
    - Supervision Council of State Board of Education - Old Senate Chamber - Post War Planning, 1944 March 24 (Box 474)
    - Taxes - Budget, 1943 February 9 (Box 474)
    - Trade Union Courier, Article for, 1944 August 23 (Box 474)
    - Traffic Safety Award Dinner., 1943 May 11 (Box 474)
    - Uncle Jim's Victory Garden - Interview on WTIC, 1944 August 25 (Box 474)
    - Vacation, 1943 June 29 (Box 474)
    - Vermont Republican State Convention - Montpelier, Vermont, 1944 May 17 (Box 474)
    - War Bond Broadcast, 1944 February 14 (Box 474)
    - War Council, 1943 February 16 (Box 474)
    - War Council, 1943 March 16 (Box 474)
    - War Council, 1943 June 8 (Box 474)
    - War Council Broadcast from Scovill Manufacturing Co., WTBY - Manpower, 1944 December 16 (Box 474)
    - War Finance Meeting - Hartford Club, 1944 October 18 (Box 474)
    - War Fund - Hartford Club, 1945 March 9 (Box 474)
    - War Fund Campaign - WICC - Bridgeport, Bushnell Memorial, 1943 October 13 (Box 474)
    - War Bond Drive - Station WTIC - Hartford and Nationwide -, 1945 October 26 (Box 474)
    - War Gardens, 1943 May 11 (Box 474)
    - War Gardens - Driving Ban - Stations WTIC, WICC, WELI -, 1943 May 25 (Box 474)
    - Waterbury Girls" Club - Jane Dillon - Interview Station WTIC, 1944 May 12 (Box 474)
    - Women of the State in Regard to Women and War Work -, 1943 February 2 (Box 474)
    - Work of the General Assembly, War Council - Housing - Health - Child Care - Old Age Tax - Post-War Planning, 1943 March 23 (Box 474)
    - Radio WNAB - Bridgeport, 1944 August 29 (Box 474)
    - New London, 1944 September 12 (Box 474)
    - Speech by Mrs. Raymond E. Baldwin Re: Red Cross, 1946 March 22 (Box 474)
    - Baldwin - Bricker - Republican Post-War Policy Association - Mackinac Island, 1943 September 6 (Box 474)
    - Speech by Governor Dwight Griswold - Nebraska - Republican State Convention, 1944 August 7 (Box 474)
    - Speech delivered by Brig. Gen. H. F. - Meeting of Newspaper Publishers and Radio Station Operators - Hartford, 1944 December 22 (Box 474)
    - Speech by Commander Harold E. Stassen (Box 474)
    - Army-Navy "E" Awards, 1943-1944 (Box 474)
    - Miscellaneous Republican Speeches, 1946 (Box 474)
    - Republican Campaign - Windham County Republican Women's Association, 1944 September 28 (Box 474)
    - Republican Candidate for Governor Radio Speech, 1944 October 3 (Box 474)
    - Republican Campaign Speeches - Radio Broadcast, Friday, October 6, 1944, 1944 October 6 (Box 474)
    - Republican Campaign Radio Address - Station WTIC, 1944 October 22 (Box 474)
    - Republican Campaign, 1944 November 3 (Box 474)
    - Republican Campaign Radio - Station WTIC - Hartford, 1944 November 6 (Box 474)
    - Republican Campaign Radio Address - WICC, 1944 October 19 (Box 474)
    - Republican Post-War Policy Association, 1943 September 6 (Box 474)
  - State Boundary Lines (Box 475)
  - State Chemists (Box 475)
  - State Farm for Women - Niantic (Box 475)
  - State Flag (Box 475)
  - State Guard (Box 475)
  - State Institutions (Box 475)
  - State Institutions Re: Fire Hazards (Box 475)
  - State Planning Board (Box 475)
  - State Song (Box 475)
  - State Veterans Advisory Committee (Box 475)
  - State's Attorneys (Box 475)
  - State's Rights [Includes material re: an Equal Rights Amendment for Connecticut] (Box 475)
  - Statute Revision Commission (Box 475)
  - Statute Revision Department (Box 475)
  - Stevens Case (Box 475)
  - Stonington Special Election (Box 475)
  - Stratford Department of Education (Box 475)
  - Stratford - Motor Bus Service (Box 475)
  - Suffield Academy (Box 475)
  - Superior Court (Box 475)
  - Supreme Court (Box 475)
  - Surplus War Materials - Mailing List (Box 475)
  - Tax Dept. (Box 475)
  - Taxes (Box 475)
  - Teachers' Association (Box 475)
  - Teachers' Retirement (Box 475)
  - Terryville Probate Court (Box 475)
  - Think Magazine article by Governor Baldwin (Box 475)
  - Torrington Historical Society (Box 475)
  - Town Courts (Box 475)
  - Trade School (Box 475)
  - Trade School - Bridgeport (Box 475)
  - Traffic Commission (Box 475)
  - Transportation (Box 475)
  - Treasury Department (Box 475)
  - Trumbull Airport (Box 475)
  - Tuberculosis Commission (Box 476)
  - Typewriter Companies - Royal and Underwood - Re Production of Typewriters Again (Box 476)
  - Unemployment Commission (Box 476)
  - United Airlines Inauguration (Box 476)
  - United China Relief (Box 476)
  - United China Relief - Celebration of Thirty-Third Birthday of the Republic of China, 1944 October 10 (Box 476)
  - United Nations Committee (Box 476)
  - U[nited] N[ations] O[rganization] Committee and Meeting (Box 476)
  - U[nited] N[ations] O[rganization] Letters from People (Box 476)
  - U[nited] N[ations] O[rganization] Luncheon Meeting, 1946 February 26 (Box 476)
  - U[nited] N[ations] O[rganization] Luncheon - Cancelled, 1946 March 26 (Box 476)
  - U[nited] N[ations] O[rganization] Luncheon - New Haven Lawn Club, 1946 June 13 (Box 476)
  - U[nited] N[ations] O[rganization] Site Committee (Box 476)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (Box 476)
  - United States Military Academy (Box 476)
  - United States Time Corporation - Middlebury, Connecticut (Box 476)
  - United Temperance Party (Box 476)
  - Unity and Amity, Governor's Com[mission] on (Box 476)
  - University of Connecticut, 1943 (Box 477)
  - University of Connecticut, 1944 (Box 477)
  - University of Connecticut, 1945 (Box 477)
  - University of Connecticut, 1946 (Box 477)
  - University of Connecticut Board of Trustees, An Act Defining the Powers and Duties (Box 477)
  - University of Connecticut Fort Trumbull Correspondence - Re: Using for Housing (Box 477)
  - University of Connecticut Industrial Management and Labor Institute (Box 477)
  - University of Connecticut Institute of Labor - Management - Relationships Dept. of Conn. (Box 477)
  - University of Connecticut Proposed Dental School (Box 477)
  - University of Connecticut Proposed Medical School (Box 477)
  - U. S. O. (Box 477)
  - U. S. O. - War Savings (Box 477)
  - V-E Day (Box 477)
  - Vermont Chamber of Commerce (Box 477)
  - Veterans of Foreign Wars (Box 477)
  - Veterans' Home Commission (Box 477)
  - Veterans' Home, Newington (Box 477)
  - [Veterans' Reemployment and Advisory Commission] Gray Committee College Training (Box 477)
  - [Veterans' Reemployment and Advisory Commission] Gray Committee - Correspondence, 1943 (Box 477)
  - [Veterans' Reemployment and Advisory Commission] Gray Committee - Correspondence, 1944 (Box 477)
  - [Veterans' Reemployment and Advisory Commission] Gray Committee - Correspondence, 1945 (Box 478)
  - [Veterans' Reemployment and Advisory Commission] Gray Committee - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 478)
  - [Veterans' Reemployment and Advisory Commission] Gray Committee - Education of Returning Veterans (Box 478)
  - [Veterans' Reemployment and Advisory Commission] Gray Committee - 1943 Committees, Post War Plans, New Release, Speeches, Minutes (Box 478)
  - [Veterans' Reemployment and Advisory Commission] Gray Committee - 1944 Minutes, Speeches, Community Plans, News Releases, Gov.'s Conference January 21, 1944 (Box 478)
  - [Veterans' Reemployment and Advisory Commission] Gray Committee 1945 Minutes, Budget, News Releases, Veterans" Centers (Box 478)
  - [Veterans' Reemployment and Advisory Commission] Gray Committee 1946 Minutes, News Releases, Dinner February 27, 1946, Advisory Committees (Box 478)
  - [Veterans' Reemployment and Advisory Commission] Gray Committee Local Adjustment and Readjustment Committees (Box 478)
  - [Veterans' Reemployment and Advisory Commission] Gray Committee Membership (Box 478)
  - [Veterans' Reemployment and Advisory Commission] Gray Committee Rehabilitation Assoc. (Box 478)
  - Veterans' Service Center (Box 478)
  - Veterinary, Board of Registration and Examination (Box 478)
  - Veto Messages, 1943 (Box 478)
  - Veto Messages, 1945 (Box 478)
  - Victory Book Campaign (Box 478)
  - Victory War Bond Drive Station WTIC, 1945 December 7 (Box 478)
  - V-J Day (Box 478)
  - Vocational Counseling Service, Inc. (Box 478)
  - Voluntary Work Seekers (Box 478)
  - Voting Laws (Box 478)
  - War Chest Campaign (Box 479)
  - War Council (Box 479)
  - War Council - Absenteeism [folder and one black notebook] (Box 479)
  - War Council - An Act Establishing the Conn. War Council (Box 479)
  - War Council - Administrator (Box 479)
  - War Council - Agriculture (Box 479)
  - War Council - Air Raid Protection (Box 479)
  - War Council - Aircraft Warning Service (Box 479)
  - War Council - Award Committee (Box 479)
  - War Council - Blackout and Dimout (Box 479)
  - War Council - Budget (Box 479)
  - War Council - Canning (Box 479)
  - War Council - Care of Children of Working Mothers (Box 479)
  - War Council - Children and Youth in Wartime (Box 479)
  - War Council - Civilian Defense [2 folders] (Box 479)
  - War Council - Civilian War Activities (Box 479)
  - War Council - Committee on Committees (Box 479)
  - War Council - Communications (Box 479)
  - War Council - Consumer Committee (Box 479)
  - War Council - Consumer Education (Box 479)
  - War Council - Consumer Information (Box 479)
  - War Council - Dentistry (Box 479)
  - War Council - Education (Box 479)
  - War Council - Emergency Medical Service (Box 479)
  - War Council - Engineering (Box 479)
  - War Council - Evacuation (Box 479)
  - War Council - Farm Labor (Box 479)
  - War Council - Fire Protection (Box 479)
  - War Council - Food (Box 479)
  - War Council - 4-H Club Activities (Box 479)
  - War Council - Fuel [2 folders] (Box 480)
  - War Council - Fuel - Weekly Reports (Box 480)
  - War Council - Gas Protection (Box 480)
  - War Council - Home Preservation of Food, Committee on (Box 480)
  - War Council - Hospitalization (Box 480)
  - War Council - Housing (Box 480)
  - War Council - Industrial Hygiene and Medicine (Box 480)
  - War Council - Legal (Box 480)
  - War Council - Letters to Various Committees and Members of War Council (Box 480)
  - War Council - Library [Re: Connecticut Library Association Representative sitting on Council] (Box 480)
  - War Council - Local War Activities (Box 480)
  - War Council - Manpower [3 folders] (Box 480)
  - War Council - Manpower - Letters Re: Awards for Low Absenteeism (Box 480)
  - War Council - Manufacturing (Box 480)